<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table></csh_table>
		<description>Help for the views</description>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
		
			<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsSectionTitle.description">This section is used to specify the views associated with your extension.</label>
			
			<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsItem.title.description">Set the name of your view.</label>
			
			<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsItem.type.description">Use the selector to set the type of the wiew. It is either "List", "Single", "Edit" or "Update".</label>

			<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsItem.viewTitleBar.description">The content will be displayed as the title bar of the view.
If markers ###fieldName### are used, they will be replaced by the label associated with the fieldname for a list view. For single or edit views, they will be replaced by the value in the main table by default. 
. Use ###tableName.fieldName### if you want to access to a field which is in another table.
. By default the raw content of the table is displayed. Use ###render[fieldName]### or ###render[tableName.fieldName]### when rendering is required like for dates or selector boxes.
Localization by means of the file locallang.xml can be used with $$$tag$$$ which will be replaced by its value according to the configuration language.
The marker $$$label[fieldName]$$$ will be replaced by the fieldName title according to the localization. By default, the main table is assumed. Use $$$label[tableName.fieldName]$$$ if necessary.</label>

			<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsItem.itemTemplate.description">Template for the "List", "Update" or "Print" views. The fields to include are defined using markers ###fieldName###.
markers ###tablename.fieldname### can also be used. In this case, no processing is performed, the marker is replaced by the value in the selected row.

In the case of a view "Update" or "Print", markers ###field[fieldName, label]### generate the display of the label (localization can be used with $$$tag$$$ or $$$label[fieldName]$$$), the current value of field "fieldName" and an input element for update.
markers ###newfield[fieldName, label]### generate the display of the label and an input element for the field "fieldName". In both cases, label and field will be wrapped with default CSS classes
. updateCol1 to updateCol4 for an "Update view" (respectively the label, the previous value, the input value, the checkbox),
. printCol1 and printCol2 for a "Print view" (respectively the label, the field).
If you do not want this wrapping, just use $$$label[fieldName]$$$ for the label and ###field[fieldName]### for the field. </label>

			<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsItem.folders.description">This field is used to define folders associated with the "Single" and "Edit" views. Click on the icon to add a folder and fill its label.
If the label is defined in the file locallang.xml, it will be translated to the selected language.
You can delete or reorganize the folder order using delete, up and down icons.</label>

	<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsItem.folders.configuration.description">Folder parameters can be added. Each parameter should be under the format:
parameter=value;

. editAdminPlus = 1;
Make the folder editable in an input form, if the user has the "Admin+" right. To be an "Admin" user, the user's TSConfig must contain a line as follows:
extKey_Admin=value 
where extKey is the extension key and value is one of the possible value of the "Input Admin Field" defined in the flexform associated with the extension.
The user becomes an "Admin+" user, if his TSConfig contains a line as follows:
extKey_Admin=value+

. cutIf = fiedname=value;
The folder is cut if the field is equal to the given value.

. cutIf = ###group=group_name###;
The folder is cut if the group name is a valid group for the current record. It checks the usergroup field in the local table if any. 

. cutIf = ###group!=group_name###;
The folder is cut if the group name is not a valid group for the current record. It checks the usergroup field in the local table if any.

. cutIf = ###usergroup=group_name###;
The folder is cut if the group name is a valid group for the current user. 

. cutIf = ###usergroup!=group_name###;
The folder is cut if the group name is not a valid group for the current user.

Instead of using cufIf attributes, you can also use showIf attributes (only with "plus" library type). In such as case, the condition tells when to show the folder.</label>

			<label index="LLL:EXT:sav_library_kickstarter/Resources/Private/Language/locallang.xml:kickstarter.viewsItem.addPrintIcon.description">If set, a print icon is added to the view.</label>

		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>
